

Jonathan Wong FRONT-END DEVELOPER

818-821-9743 jonyoung1998@gmail.com 2700 S Woodlands Village Blvd Ste 300-305 Flagstaff, AZ 86001

An energetic, enthusiastic Eagle Scout and Front-End Developer with proven experience as a freelance developer trained at Codecademy in helping companies create and maintain a better code base for reusability. Capable of continuous learning from senior developers while still nurturing junior developers. Experience in driving projects forward as the development team leader, facilitating projects from concept to launch. Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills on larger development teams. Eager to tackle more complex problems and continue to find ways to maximize user efficiency.

Skills:

- Languages HTML CSS JavaScript Python
- Libraries React jQuery Redux
- Frameworks Angular.js Node.js
- Testing Jest

Experience:

Front-End Developer Codecademy Freelance March 2023- Present/ Remote

Designed and implemented Portfolio Website, Reddit App, Front-End App with React/Redux, Web Navigator, web applications along with 3rd-party software integrations

Eagle Scout Boy Scouts of America May 2010- Present

Boy Scout troop patrol leader, Order of the Arrow representative. Planned, developed, and gave leadership to others in service projects. Live the Scout oath and Scout law in everyday life by exceeding expectations. Always does what is right, works hard to get ahead and always treats people of other religions with respect. High levels of planning and preparedness. Committed to setting and achieving personal, professional, spiritual, and financial goals. Merit badges include first aid, kayaking, canoeing, astronomy, citizenship in the nation, rifle shooting, pottery, art, wilderness survival, environmental science, soil and water, emergency preparedness, fingerprinting, personal management, personal fitness, communication, citizenship in the world, swimming, camping, citizenship in the community, and family life

Rental Coordinator Stellantis -Planet Chrysler Dodge Jeep Ram FIAT of Flagstaff · Full-time Aug 2019 - Present · 3 yrs 4 mos Flagstaff, Arizona, United States

Deliver exceptional customer experience by acting with a customer-first attitude. Made personal connections, engaged and educated customers, asked open-ended questions and listened to establish trust and build lasting relationships. Exude confidence with clients when sharing product knowledge and solutions when preparing, records and submitting warranty claims to the factory and/or distributor and reconciles them accordingly. Excellent communication skills - in person and over the phone - with proven ability to tailor features and benefits of products/services to customers with differing needs when processing warranty claims on a timely basis for each franchise or distributor. Strong desire and ability to influence, educate, and connect customers to technology when processing all warranty paperwork to ensure proper documentation. Possess drive, initiative, and knowledge to provide financial options for customers using a consultative approach when reconciling all warranty receivables with payments through the appropriate accounting schedule. Ability to learn products, services, and procedures quickly and accurately; deliver solutions that make factory warranty products work together. Operates within established risk parameters/tolerances and meets internal/external risk and compliance obligations, including completion of required training criteria required by factory or distributor. Professional, thorough, and organized with strong follow-up skills when following up on payment of outstanding claims. Engage and partner with team members and other lines of business to offer most appropriate products with body shop warranty claims, all service records as required by the warrantor, arranges for parts to be shipped to the factory and coordinate all factory recalls and bulletins.

Night Auditor Marriott Hotels · Part-time Jul 2021 - Feb 2022 · 8 mos Sedona, Arizona, United States

As a Night Auditor I analyze all revenue streams into the hotel and maintain effective controls over and the reporting of Income Audit in accordance with objectives set by the Director of Finance and Front Office Manager. Ensuring Internal Controls are kept to the highest standard and acting as a liaison between reception and the Finance team is key to my job.

In this position, excellent customer skills were important as the position is guest-facing and based at the Front Desk. My duties include a night receptionist role.

In addition, my work involved ensuring that all systems are balanced and ready for the night run, including Mini-bar, Pay TV, Telephones, Internet, and all other revenue. Critical to my role is to Check all Adjustments, Allowances, and credit card refunds for appropriateness and backup. Also, I Check all City Ledger invoices, Reconcile Micros systems to hotel PMS. Reconcile credit card systems.

I am the link between the finance department and the rest of the hotel during the night and am responsible for advising on and ensuring the hotel complies fully with all audits. My shift pattern varies over the week with the start time at 11.00 pm finishing at 7.30 am.

Barista Starbucks · Part-time Jul 2020 - Jul 2021 · 1 yr 1 mo Sedona, Arizona, United States

As a Barista in a team-oriented work environment, my duties included making hand-crafted coffee and tea drinks while providing superior customer service. The role includes coordinating Point of Sale

(POS) System and coffee brewing systems in a high-volume environment. My daily goal is to provide customer-obsessed fast and friendly service while generating the most revenue for the store.

Video Editor
Famous Players Part-time
Jul 2017 - Present · 5 yrs 5 mos
Burbank, CA

Part-time/freelance editor with a reliable internet connection and a quiet workspace free of disruptions. Provide excellent customer service, by video edits, trailers, TV campaigns, digital spots, special content, and in-house reels. Proven track record of excellent customer quality and productivity expectations. Excellent judgment in solving critical problems. Handles a variety of customer issues and functions as a creative voice for creative direction and crafting narrative short-form assets. Thinks outside the box & takes initiative. Collaborate very closely with Senior Producers and Creative Directors on all creative campaigns. Performs other duties and assignments including administrative, special projects. Able to communicate the artistic vision with partners and bring ideas to life. Stay in close communication with Creative Producers to manage deadlines and edit all campaigns according to client notes. Team player with the ability to self-manage and organize workloads around tight deadlines. Work with Post Production teams to troubleshoot hardware and software technical issues as required. Maintain and follow through on ongoing customer concerns until the issue is resolved. Create content that meets all deadlines and satisfies the client's creative direction. Ability to adapt to a fast-paced changing environment. Transform existing content into supplemental and ancillary video assets such as episode cutdowns, sizzles, compilations, outtake reels, and mobile formatted video vignettes. Experience with Windows and MS Office applications. Experienced with Premiere Pro or Final Cut Pro, to insert music, narration and dialogue, and sound effects to a video. Basic knowledge of motion graphics authoring software (After Effects). Proactively self-educates and maintains expectations regarding training and courses. Address tasks promptly. Maintains a level of professionalism that exceeds that of our customer's expectations. Receptive to constructive feedback.

The Chicken Lady Assistant Event Manager May 2012 – June 2017

Met aggressive Service Level Agreements to ensure timely communication to all levels of the business. Contributed to the success of projects that impact our stakeholders. Coordinated internal resources and third parties/vendors for the flawless execution of projects. Developed project scopes and objectives, involving all relevant stakeholders and ensuring technical feasibility. Developed a detailed project plan to track progress. Managed the relationship with the client and all stakeholders. Created and maintained comprehensive project documentation. Run regular project meetings with clear agenda, objectives and next steps. Negotiated and consolidated project schedules between project teams.

U.S. Army Junior Reserve Officers' Training Corps (JROTC) Sergeant First Class (E-7) Wolf Pack Battalion Van Nuys High School 2012-2016

Lead, guided, and mentored teams of new cadets to motivate them to achieve unit goals and trained them how to work as a unit. Made tough decisions during critical moments. Mastered verbal and non-verbal communications by empowering others and sharing information with the team. High level of personal discipline that was shared and encouraged with the unit commanded. Lead by example

for other team members to follow. Listen more than speak to learn input. Flexible and always looked for ways to improve. An attitude of perseverance and never giving up.

Education

- Codecademy Front-End Engineer
- Graduate Van Nuys High School Los Angeles, CA.

Technology Summary Skills:

- Languages HTML CSS JavaScript Python
- Libraries React jQuery Redux
- Frameworks Angular.js Node.js
- Testing Jest
- Able to effectively use the complete Microsoft Office Suite and Google Suite